Go Jordan and Mari! Tell the truth! Are you kidding?
Do you wanna know?
Whoa, are you good, dude?
Intense question.
In Noah's defense, everyone's been wondering.
You're together like 24-7.
Word on the street is someone from another class spotted you two at the summer festival together.
For real?
Yeah, we were there. It's a summer staple. Get a grip.
A summer staple?
You know I'm all about that crap! No invite, bro!
That's like X-tier bonding!
Hey, answer me, man!
The answer is no! We aren't! I mean, we hang out, but no, we aren't dating!
Your costume is totally drenched. Let's find a towel.
Yeesh, the crowd was a literal nightmare.
Maureen!
What the?
Gotta run!
What a shame. They'd make a cute couple.
Right?
I'm trying to make you king of the dang microphone!
I wanna sing too, dude!
Hey, yo!
Of course we aren't dating.
No chance.
She's way out of my league.
Just look at me.
I know we're not official or anything.
But did he really need to shut it down like some nasty rumor?
Thinking back, when Juju brought it up that one time, he did the exact same thing.
What did I do wrong?
Why do you hate me?
Just kill me now.
Huh?
You owe me a little chat.
Uh...
I'm really sorry, I...
Aw, you promised you would come, remember?
Get here already, you have the voice of an angel!
Huh?
You're saving Maureen from all the randos that hit on her.
Get real.
How many times do I have...
Uh...
Leave her alone!
Remember? Get here already, you have the voice of an angel!
You're saving Maureen from all the randos that hit on her.
Get real. How many times do I have-
Leave her alone! Just pick on me instead!
That's weirdo!
Aft criticism!
Please, you'll have fun. I'm not half as interesting as she is.
Still, I'll do my very best! I can even be your punching bag!
I'm begging you, pick on me!
Let Kitagawa go!
Am I crazy? Or does this kid really think you're hitting on her?
You're kidding! I never!
Believe me, pal, your girl isn't my cup of tea, get me?
Wait a second...
You guys... met before?
Your friends?
They're both employees at the salon I go to. They're nice guys.
You just caught him mid-lecture.
That makes me sound so rude! All I'm trying to do is help her! Look at those ends!
Turn the flight iron down or you'll seriously regret it! We'll give you that killer treatment and be clustered right down the drain!
And what do you think you're wearing, young lady?
I don't know if they're going to be very happy when his favorite body is...
That's right. You must be Dojo.
Yeah, that's me.
I'm just your purple warning, so don't go yapping about how I'm me!
Of course not! You're like the friendly guy I've ever made!
You're a stepmother!
I'm the princess and you know it!
So you heard that?
Yes, because you wanted me to hear it!
I very much did not.
They say lies again with evil!
They say a little white lie never hurts!
She's got claws, big boy, so back up!
Please don't freak yourself out.
Goof-ups like that happen to literally everyone.
I don't know.
Well, I do.
Promise me you'll take them up on that haircut, okay?
That's a super big win.
Sure, but I was so rude and just kept digging the hole deeper.
Something must be seriously wrong with me.
Why am I like this?
Maybe I should see a doctor.
At the end of the day, he was just trying to protect me.
What was that?
So...
Kitagawa?
Huh?
Yeah?
Sup?
Are you mad at me?
Did I do something wrong?
Why do you ask?
Just now, you were...
The Avery tongue-clicking thing!
What? No, I didn't add anything!
But you must have made some kind of sound!
What was that weird noise?
I... I can't tell you that!
Wait up, Kitagawa!
It's clear you're mad at me!
Tell me what I did so I can apologize!
I just told you I didn't!
Huh?
It's clear you're mad at me!
Tell me what I did so I can apologize!
I just told you I didn't!
Huh?
Uh...
Now I'm still trying to find a way, but
I'm going to show you the light
I'm going to call you the light
I don't know what to do
I have some sad news
Kitagawa will be absent today
What da heck is going on with her, Honechon?
She called the office this morning
Hey Hone, girl, it's Kitagawa
My, you better stay in bed, poor darling.
That's ouchy.
She never gets sick.
It's gotten cold outside very quickly,
so make sure to stay bundled up and healthy.
All right, let's get started with class.
I'll be handing out some materials,
so please pass them back when you're done.
He asked me to watch his apartment
until he got back in town.
I immediately accepted.
Right, very good.
Your turn, Gojo.
Gojo.
On the board, we have a right triangle
with vertices A, B, and C.
Let's start by determining the lengths of A, C, and B, C.
When you have an acid
that almost completely ionizes in water,
like hydrochloric acid,
we refer to it as strong.
There are other acids that only partially ionize in water.
What?
Gojo?
Wait, school's already over?
No, it's not even noon yet.
Huh?
Then why are you here?
You live alone.
I started worrying about you getting medicine,
and a sick person shouldn't have to prepare their own food.
I knew I could be useful.
It felt wrong to just sit there in class,
so...
I...
I faked being sick and left the school early.
Uh...
Uh, Kitagawa!
Your clothes are drenched in sweat.
Let's get you changed.
Uh...
Are there clean clothes in here?
Mm-hmm.
Anything in that basket should be fine.
Styling-y style, man.
Ah!
This is so personal.
I should just close my eyes and grab something.
I'm sorry!
Forgive me!
Think you can get yourself changed?
Let's see how you do with this.
I'm so sorry!
Is it too hot?
I'm fine.
Temperature okay?
It's perfect.
I'm glad to hear it.
Here.
I went and added a little bit of ginger to help get you warmed up.
Now that you got some down, you can take your ma-
I was stuck here, and I didn't have any food or way to get sober.
I thought I was dying.
I thought I was eating and crying at the same time.
I'm sure you'll feel a lot better as soon as the medicine starts to work.
You rest.
I can clean up.
So...
I'm sorry.
I'm right here.
Ko-Chul?
Yes?
Just wanted to say it.
Sure.
Your fever's gone down.
I feel way less dead.
I think I'll go see the doctor tomorrow.
There are some leftovers in the fridge for you.
You can have some later if you like.
Thanks.
You're the bestest.
Huh?
Maureen!
You got it now!
It's the besties.
Oh, man.
If they see me here,
they'll get the wrong idea again.
I didn't consider them coming by.
I'll go hide out on the balcony.
Huh?
For why, though?
I lied so I could leave school early.
I can just wait for them to leave.
Hey!
You are taking care of me.
I think they'll get it.
Yay!
You lied!
You're hot!
You brought ice cream and sports cream!
It's chilly this high up in the air.
I could catch a cold.
I can't...
I did.
shovel peel peel peel...
I don't know.
If you need our water
You'd have to throw up or don't put it in the air.
Take a cold,
vs...
If you haven't done where it should be,
you're gone.
Oh, my God.
It's so pretty.
I swear, just looking at it might heal me.
I can't believe we get to do a shoot in the aquarium.
Acosta's the best.
The last time we did this, it was all in the plaza in the park.
You can also walk around and check out the shops while in cosplay.
I want to see the little honors in my queen.
Hey, Kitagawa, would you slow down?
No!
Huh?
Um, Kitagawa, is something the matter?
Super love, Kitagawa!
Please, Super love, Kitagawa!
From Coslove, am I dreaming?
Face Idols! Cosmic Lovers!
Coslove for short.
A simulation game where the player manages their idol
and raises her to be the best in the universe.
You can actually date the idols, too.
But if the company, fans, or other idols find out,
you'll get fired.
And it'll be game over.
What's worse, you and your idol break up.
Oh my gosh, you're literally her!
You're so precious, it hurts!
Your cuteness level is an SSR!
Cuteness level SSR?
Also, Hoshimori Idol High's uniforms
are the most adorable thing ever!
The checker design and the frilly bow
are so quintessentially idle!
Is it this super room? We're really here!
I'll protect you with my life!
Hoshimori Idol High?
I'm so sorry for getting myself all hyped up, miss!
You okay down there?
Oh, uh, the truth is,
I kind of dropped the hook from my skirt.
Oh, shoot!
Where do you think it might have gone?
We can probably find it
if the light hits it just right.
Um, you don't have to go through all this trouble.
It's fine.
We'll find it a lot quicker if we're all looking.
Uh-huh!
Thank you very much.
I really appreciate your help.
Just helping a cos-friend in need.
I'm just glad we were able to find it.
By the way, can I ask your cos-player name?
Sure.
It's Amane Himeno.
Miss Amane!
Oh, your name is so adorable that I'm gonna cry!
And my cos-name is Marine.
I'm Wakana Gojo.
This might be weird, but I'm curious.
Are you two partners by any chance?
Partners?
Kitagawa and I are in the same class in high school,
and I make all of her outfits.
He casually dropped Marine's real name?
So, Miss Amane, do you have anything planned after this?
And she doesn't care?
I was hoping the two of us
might be able to snag a pic together!
Of course!
I appreciate the offer, but I'm sorry.
I'm going home for today.
With my outfit like this,
I'm afraid I'm going to ruin Subaru's image.
Would you like me to fix your skirt, then?
We've had our sheriff incidents,
so I always have my sewing kit with me.
You're prepared for everything, Gojo!
But I would feel bad making you do that.
This won't take long at all.
I promise.
It's no trouble.
Well, let me take you up on your offer, then.
Great!
Let's head on back and use the changing rooms at the venue-
Oh, wait!
I can't go into the women's dressing room.
Oh!
You want me to just bring you the skirt, then?
The men's dressing room is fine.
You can't!
It's against the rules to use the wrong dressing room!
It says so here in the pamphlet!
It's okay, because I'm really a guy.
Here you go.
Thanks.
I'll get to work.
If it's okay, I would like to touch up my makeup.
Sure.
Go ahead.
Wow!
This looks awesome!
Himeno doesn't look like a guy at all.
I wonder if it's because of his makeup or how he acts.
How does he look so much like a girl?
Liquid glue!
Wait, is that why?
This liquid glue is so important that he has to carry it around with him at all times.
But if that's the case, where is he using it in his cosplay?
I don't get it.
Where does the glue go?
Glue.
Come on.
Is something wrong?
Oh, no.
Ah, nothing at all.
Just about done sewing.
Focus, man.
Maureen?
Huh?
It was a ringer!
Oh, it's so good to see you again!
Right back at you!
The pics you took of me were absolutely amazing!
Really, I'm glad you like them!
I have to say, you're looking super adorable today!
You're adding Gears back onto my life!
Why, thank you, Suzuka!
I can't believe I get to see such a cute cosplay just by paying the entrance fee!
It's basically free!
That's Shizuku-tan's Humiliation Cafe outfit!
Like it jumped off the screen!
Suzuka, you know what Slippery Girls is?
It's actually because of you that I played it.
And it was so awesome!
That makes me soaps happy to hear!
The Great Smurts Festival was so moving!
After playing the game, I can see just how close your costume is to the real thing!
Ah!
Come to think of it, Shizuku-tan wasn't wearing any panties during the entire cultural festival
and had the menu written on her thighs!
Marine put the tallies on her legs last time even though you couldn't see them!
Don't tell me!
Um, so Marine, underneath your hakama, are you wearing any...
It's a cosplay event, so I've got shorts on!
Take a peek!
Ah!
You don't have to show me!
I believe you've been good co-wearing shorts and a flashing foe!
This is my first time participating in a cosplay event like this.
I wasn't ready, but I will be next time.
Thank you both so much for your help.
It was really no big deal.
We're actually younger than you, so there's no need to be so formal.
Well, thank you guys.
Soap around, smile!
Um, Himeno?
Hm?
In the dressing room, when you were fixing your makeup,
I thought I saw...
something that looked a lot like a tube of liquid glue in your pouch,
and I've been curious ever since, so I gotta know...
Was that...
really?
I see.
Well, it's not just that it looks like glue.
Huh?
It is glue.
I was right!
Whoa, what do you use that for?
You know how you stick your wigs, bangs, or side hair to your face?
Stick?
Just like this.
Who's doing it?
And it sticks!
Curly, runny, sticky, sticky.
Oh my gosh, what?
That doesn't irritate your skin?
Well, it doesn't bother me, but the proper stuff is better.
See, my bone structure is different from my curls,
so I do my best to change the shape of my face using my wigs.
It's a trick I use for all my close-up pics.
What?
Show me!
I'd love to see them!
Sure, here you go.
I've got nothing to hide, so take a look.
Whoa!
What the heck?
You're too cute!
For real?
These are awesome!
Looking at it again, is my pose unnatural?
Maybe it isn't curly enough.
Oh, it's def's girly enough.
See?
I do the same pose.
Marine, you're a gyaru.
It so suits you.
He uses the clothes to change his body shape
and makes full use of his skirt.
Sort of the opposite from cosplaying a guy.
But once the mic's in her hand, she never lets go.
Even on Halloween, she wouldn't...
Are you okay?
Wakara, was there a weird picture?
Not weird, but mind-blowing!
Huh?
It's just...
This chest!
How did you do it?
Get a look at those boobaronis!
Was it retouched?
Couldn't have been.
They look so natural!
No need to Photoshop anything.
You can equip boobs.
You can?
I'd be glad to show you.
Wanna see some...
boobies?
Yeah, I wanna see boobies!
What?
That's all, I want to see and share.
See ya!
Bye!
We'll see you all go!
igong
Bye!
Thank you.